Paula and Kajala back with another vlog.
[music]
Wake up.  I haven't even slept.  Why have you been sleeping
all this time?  Guys, can you believe
I haven't slept since I woke up at
one o'clock this morning until this minute. It's
12 o'clock now.
I haven't slept. I want to drink tea then go to sleep.
Why are you yawning?  Oh oh oh oh oh
baby.
Okay guys
[music]
we were ready to go outside to
leave but Amara's sister
realized that the bag she took wasn't hers. The
bags were similar. She took a bag I
don't know, Neema's,
so we have to wait again to find
her bag inside. Then we leave. I'm
sleepy and hungry. Amara, are you hungry?
Yes.   He is
calling this and that.
So yeah, let's wait.  Hey
[laughter]
[music]
guys, people are very spiritual.
This guy even knows where his son is, so he runs
after the meat.  This is broken there.
I was seeing him
standing there
[smiling]
we put the cake,
cut the cake, cut the cake, my son,
cut the cake [laughter]
cut the cake, turn it like this, turn the
cake,
I'm the one cutting on behalf of you,
Amara,
what do you want,
my lady,
happy
birthday, happy birthday, happy
birthday
to you [crying]
birthday,
this birthday boy is eating, he's
writing
[laughter]
there he's getting angry, give him a w
[beating his fist]
w
again,
hehe [laughter] why is it a
picture
of my grandfather, a song of my grandfather and
his secret, when will I see
you?
Ah [beating his fist]
whose turn is it for that child again?
Amar
ya
ya big girl
sister
eh brother
al yes I give it brother
ah why am I like a business yes I've been
thinking about it
[laughter] yes you have been yes
birthday
I am the birthday girl I explain to you
with big
big brother
[laughter]
Eh
ya mama mza chema [laughter]
ya bibi
wam [
laughter]
ah I'm really tired it's not true [laughter]
bana
[music]
al
[laughter]
[beating the drum]
Good morning.  Let me give you updates.  Yesterday
we arrived in Moshi.  When we arrived in Moshi,
we went to my mother's house because the
hotel check-in time was around
9am and we arrived at 6pm. So we
came here and slept to get some sleep.
It was already late.  We said that if we leave
here for Arusha, we will arrive at night and
enjoy ourselves at the hotel.
So we slept here and ate meat
because it was a child's birthday and we cut a
cake.  We had so much fun and enjoyed it so much.
So it's time to live right now.  Let's go to
Arusha Grand Maria.  Guys, this is my
little mother, I know many of you know her.  mh
starts my mother follows she is
very beautiful she has a mouth she has a farm but here she
pretends she is ashamed
m
hi guys
we enjoyed it so much yesterday mani thank you
okay mi I am glad to see you soon again
smoke i am so
happy to see you guys come
again and again I will not
come
your family is everything so
yeah family comes first love
Hi as Paulo said
our Easter we had planned to
come here but we came the second Easter
to spend time with Dory so we enjoyed it
now it has arrived our trip to
Arusha
to go to Ngorongoro and but
we have enjoyed it so much here we have eaten animals
so we had fun thank you Dolly
is my sister-in-law my best wifi
we call each other wifi we don't call each other sister-in-law
has received us well everyone has been happy
until i.e. all the people who came say i.e.
here i.e. we have been very
comfortable sister-in-law i.e. he is someone who
cares he stays so we thank him
very much may God bless him increase him when he reduced
S
[music]
we have arrived mani Grand Maria
we are waiting to check in he is crying
what is that mani hamara
Come to mami.
No, man, I came here to enjoy myself, I don't want any
drama like this.  I don't want to at all.
What did you do to Amara?
Tell him I'm sorry my babyara so sorry my
baby.   Do
you know how it hurts when a child rejects
you, mother,
you just video call, you want to cry,
not two, there are two invs in each room and
its inv,
you understand,
give it all to me,
so in dollars it becomes
or I combined it into one, charges
no, it's okay, okay,
then I will ask for your details, email,
phone number and below
this signature and this here,
various,
why various,
we can look at the ability, if
we can, we can find the closest ones,
we can put them in, but if it's not possible, that's all,
but we will look at the vilability
that we have, okay, yes, so,
eh,
19, why do
n't you want to know,
98, how much is that for?
98 is approaching
[music] and nothing is happening
.
[music]
Oh, these are just a few of the things I
want to take.
So what should I take?
Maybe an apple.
[music] I don't
even see what to take, man.
Oh, I don't know.  Let me just eat this,
man, it's two, so let him keep it, come and
take his two ch,
man [clearing throat] this is it,
man, you have to be, in a
civilized way,
it comes from
the cow.   You
were not awake again,
you heard them calling me boss lady [laughter]
you are being clever and I am being
sarcastic, so please
buy me
what price you are offering me
320, that
is [laughter]
that is, I have taken a lot and there is still some left
[music]
R check
kajara has the right to be two million,
really, because I
have actually ordered coffee,
man, this is our room, mother,
please don't disturb me, I haven't done a room tour,
this is not your room, this is yours
[beating and going]
that's not what we said, let's take a walk again,
I myself can't understand
so that we can finish,
man, as you see, a
suit like a suit
or let's take a presidential one,
I think, yeah, that's what has become much
better, we
won't be arguing about that,
the camera, sugar, so here we have a kitchen,
man,
of course, to cook for him,
yeah, for cooking for him, there is a
fridge, as you can see, eh, man, a
microwave.
Yeah.  This is the kitchen.  Here is the
dining room.
This is dining, guys.
Yeah.  As you can see
here
Amara is eating.  This is the sitting
room balcony.  Amara doesn't want her sister, guys,
what's wrong with her,
this is a public toilet, I
immediately cried, guys, I was happy, I didn't have any, I
got it
[music]
Oh my god.
Wow.
Hi,
as we told you, we just got down to
watch Amara, she was
crying a lot about swimming, so I did
n't carry the swimming cost, but I carried
this,
hi mommy, hi mommy, hi
Hi mommy.  Hi mom.
[music]
I told you the water was cold.  Amala is
shivering and sees that her hands are
cold.  That is, here because
my body is hot, I give it to him like a heater.  I mean, I'm turning him on
.  [laughter]
Kiss the lady.  Kisses, grandma.  Rev.  You see even
the guess fails, my grandson, do you want
to kill him or someone you know has
chest problems, he has a cold 247, what do you want to do to him,
sorry, grandma, I'll hit him and kill him, he
wants to go to the toilet,
I see him, that is, as he heard the child, he
hits the toilet, where he is, he is like, that is,
he looks at his fingers, his shoes are not like they have been
washed,
who is this
you have cut, Too much
big
yummy
pizza,
what is that margarita pizza?
Oh, there's a chicken sandwich, there's a variety
of macarons, cakes, and what's up? Ok.
[music]
Imagine someone paying for a room almost
2 point something and then you come to the
sauna and steam and they tell you you're not allowed to
record
eating this cake.  Oh, this cake is delicious.  There's only one of this
cake left, brother.   There is only one of
this cake left.
Nothing else is good.   I'm going to the
kitchen.
So who are the people who enter this
room?  That is, those
who enter the room are guests with
super hotel privileges.  Foristans
are those big people like celebrities.
uh government officials and even those who
have paid the extra amount to get this kind
of service.
Okay.
Yes.
So if you do this, just serve as
you wish.
Yes.
24 hours, not 24 hours.  The timings
change
because in the morning I open at
five:00 and at m:00.
Oh okay
we can take the drinks, there are no
hard drinks, hard drinks, there are no hards,
we had them for me.
Okay,
guys, I love those cakes.
I asked them to give me all of them because since
I arrived, I've already eaten six, I don't know.  I try try it
's very good, it's very good,
but because you don't know why we
spendi chop like vanilla, it's not very good,
tell me why, I mean, if I take a
good picture of you, then you fail, I mean, to
fulfill what my heart desires, I mean, I don't
even know how to say it. I mean, guys, if you
go look at
Frida's Instagram, I'm the one who always takes good pictures of her
.  That is, if you see a picture of him looking good, you should know that it's
me, why he can't take a
good picture of me, that is, why am I here
now, what am I doing here,
at this point, I don't even know how to say it.
I'm sad.  I am very disappointed.
Why do you want to cry?   Yes
.  you want to kill me because of
the pictures
pictures
we
put on social media pictures
we are for you you can
put on snapchat insta pictures
you crying because of pictures
[laughter]
you were born and ask me
it's not just pictures that is for me I'm the one who listens and
tells you that is I'm
surprised because of because until now I've
called Hamisa I've called her I've told her I've told her please help me teach her to
take pictures.  He told me
that taking pictures is a talent,
yes I am Hamisa, we went like that until 45,
he only took five pictures of me but imagine what
I found out now you guys are taking
50 pictures of me and they are all [ __ ], that is why
why are you doing this to me, don't take
pictures, why do you have to take
pictures,
no, I have to shoot, why shouldn't I shoot, that is,
pictures are my life, that is, pictures are
everything to [laughter], that is, better
not to eat but wealth so that I can get what
I want, guys, that is, until I tremble,
that is why I announced to them and told them
I want a friend who knows how to take pictures,
but until today I haven't found Omari, you have to
find him, that is,
Omari himself knows, that is, wood,
eh, Omari has to, because of that job, if you travel
somewhere, find a
photographer for you when you are traveling, I am not a
photographer, Kajala Masanja is not a photographer,
so I believe it is not and shooting,
man, for pictures, I don't believe it
because it is not the eyes, the ears, it is
every day, you want me to shoot them, I don't shoot them
[clearing my throat] I don't like these,
these are pictures, you have been shot [laughter]
until I laughed, mother  It's not good, that is,
why are you guys doing
this to me? It's not true, it's a picture you left. It's
not you. Everything you tell me, I'm not
doing it to you. It's
you, mom.
You're taking
all the pictures of me. I'm taking good pictures.
Why are you unable to take good pictures of me?
Now you're making me unable to
go to Mbugani tomorrow.
[clearing throat] guys, I have mixed
feelings. I'm crying while laughing. You're making me
unable to go to Bugani. If you don't take pictures of me, that
is, we've made a trip there,
then I won't get what I want.
Those people who are guides
don't know anything.
So we have to find him. We have to take pictures of the
best there. Let's go and shoot him. Let's go to the airport.
Who will we find at this hour? Let's go with him at dawn. Who will we find? You're really wronging me. I'm
telling you the truth. Let me
google the best. Let's take
pictures of him. Let's go with him
again. Especially you, my mom.
Guys. But if there's anyone who
knows how to take pictures the way
I want, please
come forward. But for now, I'm
looking for a personal photographer who
I can travel with every time I
go. He should be there. He should
know what I want.  What do I want, I don't understand, come on,
take a shower since this afternoon, we've
all taken a shower
[laughter],
you're going to tell me, don't laugh, I'm
pregnant, we've taken a shower, we've given you
pajamas,
where did you take a shower, did you change your pajamas,
why are you confused, you
people haven't taken a shower, you're telling me I took a shower
again, where are you, Paula,
where are
you, oh, yesterday, last night, you slept without taking a shower, it's cold, it's cold, what's wrong with you, man, there was a shower, but today I took a shower, we just came out of the pool, you know I really took a shower, you know, last night, why am I the only one who took a shower, everyone, Ti and her husband and her, took a shower, and you?
Hi so we are on our way to Ngorongoro
right now.  We woke up at 5 am.   It
's 1:00 am and we're still on the way.
Driver, what time will we get there?
45.
Ah so at t at t
Okay guys what do you have to say
even though it's not our first time
going to
Ngorongoro I've never gone to
Tarang but we wanted to go to
Serengeti but we missed the plane then we
went by car this is six to
seven hours we saw the weather we said we'll stay a lot
and Amara will bother us so
we thought it's better to go to Ngorongoro
because it's close
let's go
I hope we can't wait to see the
giraffe zebra I
hope Amara will bother us and she will be
excited so yeah catch you
[music]
Content content
no content to make someone's
chest
hurt how much my chest hurts I cover it like this
no I
would go down but I'm afraid those monkeys will rape me
here they don't reach I feel
their wounds don't heal this when
they rape me
their voice doesn't come out [laughter]
this noted wild an feed check man we
've reached Ngorongoro this I don't know where it is
here we've been stopped this let's take a video
and pictures or let's go you know it's
very cold it
's cold
this
cold
The pictures are giving me a chance to shoot
or take
content, hold me if I do
n't give it to you,
Maraoni,
your pictures, you, mom, come on,
subscribe,
soon, Ngorongoro, it's a video, it's a video,
okay, Hi, we met your husband, we decided to
take a video, please, you love us,
love, you see
[music]
Oh.
How many million elephants?
That is, if you hit an elephant for 40 million or if
you hit him for
40 million,
there is a sign that says
55 million giraffes. If
you marry him, he gives you a baby. Once you pay,
you also leave them.
Who is this? If you kill him, he is a chiwala. How
small is this?
What kind of meat do you see?
I think it is something like 200.
One hit,
you pay
someone who hits an antelope. If you hit him,
it is a nyumba.
Now, not if you hit him there
or if we hit a
Kamarau
flamingo. If
you drive past us, the flamingo will probably
be 10.
Who is this bird?
What is its name? A very beautiful bird. A
bard is sucking on something. It eats
carcasses. It
eats only leaves and seeds.
It looks like it is intoxicated. It lives
alone. But
this is a male. If you saw it for a while, I will tell you
where is its tail?
Oh really, they're leaving
their partner and they're leaving [laughter] they'd be
looking at nanyas
what what do you know about
birds
who birds kory bastard or sa unaj
bustardi I'll be insulting someone cor
bustard [laughter]
or another time bastard bastard or if
you go to the ward people have bad habits you've eaten
kikupu it's delicious don't say ribas
was sweet
okay
m
say you know this mother sh we'll never
feed him [laughter]
stories of stupidity
that's why this one said [laughter]
things of nyema I remembered
the teacher saying
goodbye [laughter]
what is
there some kuli
I hear there was a certain period in Mombo
where
people were afraid to eat chicken meat
because they say there are certain birds like this they
were catching yes
kibaster
not kiber there are certain other birds like this
I think maybe it could be true sa
kibas we ate at school
this one has no problem [laughter] this one is
like a chicken has no problem look at me I'm
telling you mother shinyanga still
sir what shinyanga did you study
savanna
there [laughter] kandanga dropped here
man
eh sh it's called savanna  and don't laugh,
mom, you'll feel like you're lying and
tell them that the school is called savanna
[laughter] really the school is called window the
school is called savannah really let me go to the
school is called savannah but eat that
[laughter] eat that bastard here see see the
house they're fighting the house he's fighting the house he's fighting the house he's fighting
[music]
[music] [music]
You know they're chasing these people the
turkeys
they're protecting
some birds today they're not here up there he's crying if you're
holding the meat you're frying there's some eat
take medicine today
one of them
white people food you've lost your
appetite [laughter]
salt he's deprived me
Pepper comation there's nothing lemon or
lime it's really bad
please send you a
bottle of water I want to eat rice you've had enough of
this one I haven't touched it at all
m
hivo are you smart that is
since yesterday we've been scheduled
that is we're eating [laughter]
we're scheduled for food with sugar while you're chasing that one while you're not here we do
n't understand where he is Here there you take him
down and he's
talking
I tell Idris here there  meat, I
mean, I forgot, then he came down like this,
and I washed it, it's
not
right
[music]
I don't even know if it's good
It's
B
[music] [music] [music] [
music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [music]
[music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [
music] Hello [music]
[music] [music]
[music] [music] [music
] [music] [music] [music] [music] we're just sitting here, I'm surprised you're sitting here and they're closing the clock, we have to go, we need the one who stays and the deposit, I want him to stay here, he won't be able to code if he walks [music
]
[music]
walk
you
go you I'm
afraid
first you don't hold it
that is it's not slippery as you see it don't hold it
there man it
's
[music]
we arrived here day one we couldn't
do the
tour because we had arrived it was
very late so we just went to the pool and
yesterday we also came back from where ngorongoro
we came back we were late it was 2:00 at
night so we went to sleep we woke up at this time
we had breakfast wait I'll just make it for you
man our hotel buse we have to
check out we have to go to another hotel
so let's go
[music]
hm
man that time is big imagine
there's a banana here
thank you what's this here?
This is rosemary.
Oh rosemary.
And that is lemon grass.  What is lemongrass
?
Lemon grass man
chai chai.  I don't give up on tea.
This is tea.
You are doing well with this chive.  What is chive
?
What are chives?
Ah, I know
the spring onion.
Jesus,
papaya, guys.
Here
are the coins I'm asking you to give me
for decorating food.
Oh, that's it.  Oh,
these guys are so good.  So
you see
your two types,
this one for decoration, this one
is spinach, that one is cilantro, you know
cilantro,
I know
that one and
where is it, that one is here, that one is
here,
oh, you're
under the yellow ones, what do you think,
oregano,
oregano, oregano, you know
these are the ingredients, let me give you some,
don't you know, let's get to
these, these are the ingredients that are used
for food, it's
used a lot in the pan,
everywhere, guys,
this one is called this one, this one is
called chayote,
chaote, this one is used in salads,
it gives fruit, where is it?
See below.  M
eh those gingers
here these
are gingers guys that
's ginger you see gingers
too those are flowers for
going to food or eggplants
there is
food too
but these are killing people these
no these are eaten there is
one movie I already got married eat
you want to eat
eh
let me check which one
Tarang what is tarango?
That tarragon is called tarragon.
Oh, these are still very small, this
is chicha.
Yes, it is self-destructive.
This is still a small choir.
That's more flow.  God, flowers
help prevent small ones
[music]
ston ginger is not true maybe Fanta
Fanta
Guys, this hotel is big, big,
we ourselves have other places
we had never been to, we saw today
if you saw it, I don't know, there is lemon grass and
all the makorokoro,
I don't want to leave but
we will go bankrupt, let's go to another hotel,
the bags are too many,
if we had come to move for a
whole month, what is that there?
So guys, it's time to check out Grand
Maria.  We enjoyed it very much.  Amara, did you enjoy it?
Amara, look at what you enjoyed?
Yeah.  He enjoyed it.  So guys, let's go
[to music], guys,
this guy has romantic stress.
His baby is very jealous, meaning he doesn't answer the phone
right away, he's a quarrelsome person, when he's
stressed,
say, "Your baby is jealous." He
'll come and kill me. He'll
really kill you. Why are you here, Panda?
Okay,
sorry,
how are you? He.
[music]
When I'm here, you don't want a sister,
but when I'm not here, she's gay.
Go to go to
how are you?
Hi,
Are you
okay?
Yeah.
[music]
Oh my, Amara loves this part.
He loves his
brother, what did you give him, Mr. Wanguaji?
He likes to draw or let's go
let's go baby and shine yours.  Come on, let's
go.  Come on, baby,
come on.  We came to this picture first, you just
finished it, you just
started it, you just finished it.
Oh, you're not done yet.
Okay, let's go, I'll call you back later.   Let's go
.
Okay, let's go
guys, it's time to check out.  We really enjoyed it, as he
enjoyed it, meaning the hotel is the
best.  So come along with us and see
where we're going now and what
other hotels we're going to visit.  Ciao
[music]
baby a big fan of your body let me make
sense of your body [music]
[singing]
over me.
[music]
fam
life
[music] yananya
life really wanders [music]
life
[music]
like a dream
what's good
Tanzania is ahead to see
two but
eh you want to download Yes.
Oh I have to take it home to eat
food
like these two of you
know the meat
meat meat but let's find it and much
m is
there now
amara we ask you and you
why amara here is so gentle
why is he gentle
amara is gentle in the video anak ngulu
okay pause
pa mara
why is he calm like that amara keep posing
ready
these
alf we are coming ngom
I ask for one picture
I ask for one picture Regina I wanted
one picture me and you I do
n't know
this is Paula's unasim
I shoot with Paula
[music]
very much
she herself I love them that is I have to take
home food
things 26
like these two
you know the meat meat meat meat but [music]
what does he say
[beating unyende]
Okay.
[beating]
Eh maamisha
[music]
We've arrived here, I didn't know if
we had to climb mountains to get
to the waterfalls and our questions are
very big.
So we had to change the lady or she wore a
veil.  I have to buy clothes.  These are the clothes themselves,
man,
you're trying to style yourself, you don't deserve it.
That's Tanzania but fresh.
Oh, I wanted it to be short.
Shorter.
Oh, I wanted it to be short, but
now short isn't enough for me.  The buttocks have become
very large.
Very much,
mashallah.  Mashallah.
Mashallah, believe me, if
you were to tie your shoes behind, I told
you, call me in the middle of the road, we're going to go, please put those shoes
behind. I told you, you're welcome, I want you to come back
with them, and
I've been told not to touch the edge of the grass, let's go, put
those shoes behind there, there's no
welcome, I want you,
you can fall, why?
Hey I want you to stop touching me later, guys, you'll be fine, you caught me, guys, you caught me.
No, I'm not
selling you music, Snapchat, that music
here,
that's why every filter has its own music, because
I'm already tired, that's how
we start.
They said 30 minutes.
30 minutes.
It's dangerous
and
there's no car that can follow us. The
helicopter
[laughter] maybe the helicopter [snorts]
we're not supposed to run. You can see
what
this is for today. I don't know about hiking. [laughter] It's
big. He's got to do some hiking
stuff.
Hei,
because Rohi can't carry me.
Hey, guys, that's just how it is.
S failed to record
when we were all failing to get down. I
don't know without Sehon and Roi.  And there is the
good Samaritan.
Hey, look,
why did we come here,
people from vlogs? Until now, I don't advise you
to come here. Maybe if I find waterfalls there,
things won't be difficult.
Let's go to the bag.
Maybe when we get there, we'll know.
But right now, the water freezes right there when
you get there. It's hot.   He doesn't have this
water, he will
scream,
he will love it.  Don't you know a child loves
adventure,
this child will love it,
Hamara tells me, oh my,
you see Hamara, he's not afraid of this
water, the water
is so cold, I've given you a taste,
I've shown you kindness, I would have known, I would have known,
these are the things, I'm
telling you
how I only
knew about waterfalls, that is, I used to go hiking
with my mother, it was
Christmas, I
don't know, there are places I don't remember
well, they take us to the waterfall, it's like
this, I remember we went hiking 20 20
something there,
eh, my second time but I had
forgotten because it was a long time ago,
Mom, you're really
starting
[laughter]
[beating], what's
one of them going with all of them?
follow me
no things are bad while
good
while we don't come again
why
oh enjoy you've arrived I
didn't expect I didn't expect
something good you have to pay for it
eh eh
this is it ma Eh hastarijoy
Eh you're ahead okay alf eh this is it
they can't put it there in
front like this
you feel we would know I would tell you
not to come here far you would have his nose
talking Dar es Salaam
eh sniff I would have his nose
then and those there also reception yes there that is the
stupid part that is eh
not stupid there
this is true
it's not so bad these even in
life
eh yes that's it how
I tell you k
those stones
how I tell you when I see
this beautiful place if I get good pictures when
I don't get good videos or pictures
my vlog people you see how
I struggle for you just to
get nice content for you please
pray for me don't stop ah don't stop subscribing
subscribe
that is that mother
is this
eh
[laughter]
and still
but I pray eh I pray when I
come back I come back safely guys
if you have arrived safely you will come back safely
because every time I get what then
you think eh
teacher
[music]
Guys, we just came here for pictures.
Go take pictures of them, mister, mister,
what did we come to do?
You wanted to come and
take a video. Let's
see. Let's go back
there. Come back,
mister. What time will you be dancing? Tiktok? Tiktok?
What time will you be dancing? Let's go, hold on tight. You hold on tight. Let me hold on tight. Let me hold on tight. Let me
take a video. Now let's go.
One, two, three. That's right, there's no one.
I don't know about
this video. Ah, video. Come in. Come in.
You're leaving. They're
strong. That's
strong. That's water. That's right,
move there. Move.
Ah, those long ones
wouldn't fit in your legs. Oh, the
water wouldn't be cold. I'm looking
for you.
That's adventure.
He tells me an example. He dried up. I told him. I
fell. It seems like we've fallen twice.
You failed to help someone. Oh, what's
this? I don't know. This
is a capsule. It would
be really short.
It would be hot now. Oh,
if it comes. There
are other people who said, "
If it's easy, come on,
my son, it's not cool." Uh
[music]
Roamona
I don't know what's up Jim's left here,
man,
your friend is breathing while climbing one
here, I see I'll go ahead
I'm not afraid or anything
my friend, here I go, where do I go, it's right there,  You do
n't just see K all the time
again, a cloth here,
maybe we can find a
soda bottle that's empty, it
spins well,
this is a game of truth or dare, we play here,
we play here, it ends here, that is, when he
leaves, it
shouldn't continue
[laughter], that is,
maybe in the vlog we edited it,
oh, that is, this is this, this is
not supposed to go outside of here.
Okay.
Let's sit in a good position so that the bottle
doesn't cause trouble in telling who it belongs to.
[laughter]
You're not here now, if you're
following the bottle like this, I get it, I get
the bottle straight, let's stay in a position where
chips
[clears throat], that is, I'll ask you like
truth, that is, you are being asked the truth or is it telling the
truth or doing something that you will be told.
So you will choose before you are asked a
question, you will say right now I want to
tell the truth, so you will ask a question
that requires you to tell the truth.
God's truth.
So when you say truth, it means you are
telling the real truth.  If I were to
tell you, I would dare you to take a
bottle of water and drink it without
stopping and you have to do that.  Okay?
Three two, one action.
Idris
Idris Idris this
brother this is Idris
is Idris [laughter]
Idris
truth or de
truth
what
big
and bad thing has
happened to you since 2026
since 2026 starting that is
eating away at your heart and you have never
shared it with anyone.   There is a lot of
smoke coming out of the Masai.  Ah
raising a family
[laughter]
you
tell the
truth I tell you the truth I am a
large percentage of my family in
life mother same and my mother's son
my younger parent female male female male
m
that is 70% I rely on it
who does he depend on
n Oh
that's why I got sick he is afraid to
start
coming to you because I my old man I
have been protecting the family so leave there is
no one else I am the
first bor family m and the younger ones are hesitant it's
okay so your time
eh what should
I do m I don't understand I asked him a question like
I asked you or you will ask a question
I am going around no you are asking me I am
asking you a question can someone
tell you dea
that is you ask him truth or dea he
will tell you if it is truth de for me
here I am looking for my place to stay
do it by force
where there is
no
[clearing throat] it's not mudi
[laughter]
dewezi
here there is no
one to scare
you anything you feel like calling him to do he should do if he doesn't do it he says he
has dea de let dea is the one
he gives  hela
ahah
that is if someone fails to do the dea they just have to
eh then we all share later
ask you what is
dea dea is to dare that is to tell him to do
something that you see
can be a challenge for him or
do it with a stick that is not something easy so that when he
comes out 30 later we take it
like we used here call me call me
squat five do
squat five
no sano
for paula [laughter]
is this
hands in front or here please let me show you please let me
show you an example until
you see this or do this
eh down
that is when you come back yes one please listen
to me [laughter] I
can't we pray we pray there we pray there thinking
about the stairs there that is to say I
can't tell you how I just woke up
I would do we pray
there we pray
30 there we pray there on the table we
pray there it's
not my problem but starting to hurt
now this [laughter]
put your 30 there on the table where is it
put my colleague this there you have been on strike
I will do
you for those jobs  I'm not doing it mom
[clearing throat] what's this
come here this go that one now
turn the chup
mi I'm asking for yours [laughter] where do
you like it
30 here give
me some pepe
you are being returned [laughter]
something hello there are no chips how are
you talking to who you are
Eh
if it hasn't gone here there is
no one that is
amara
matha amara is not there is mat eh
this mas truth or de
dea
eh
why don't you call
your child's father right now
tell him I love you
[laughter] call
m I asked you masa do you understand [laughter] call your
father your river tell him I love him Right now he hasn't told
me to answer.
Hey, let's
say I love you.  I didn't pick up the phone [laughter]
[ringing] you pick up the phone
you have nothing.  Call the phone.  Where is your phone
?
Pick up the phone.
Mas has hidden the phone.   I mean, you see me
standing like this, I was
saying, "This is what I want from this person."
[laughter]
I'm sure who he's calling?  Who is the father
?  Dad, I don't know who Dad is, I don't know what
Dad is clever.  There is Father Juma, Father Shedi.   Do
n't you see, mother,
put on the speaker [laughter],
sir.
Oh.
Hello
Hello [clearing throat]
Hello Hello
just tell him I love you tell him I love you
when
I love
him myself
[laughter]
I would pay him a fine
[to hit him]
I mean I would pay him a fine because
someone is not right I give him a fine they are
not right what is he talking about I am
going to tell him on the side Oya it's a game.
[laughter]
Oh, it's a game.
He's calling, he
must be calling, we must hear him, we must hear him, we must hear him, we must hear him, we must tell
him, he is a liar.   Do
n't tell him to listen to us.  Eh eh
let's hear it
hello it was a
joke it was a
joke
can
I hear you eh you say
it was a joke
what joke hasn't heard hasn't heard hasn't heard you've said it's over he'll see
on the vlog he's
calling again mom he's heard no he's heard
Paula again
Paula [laughter] you haven't messed around bro I have
n't seen the
law there are
no laws here tomorrow it won't come out mom [
laughter] this brother is not here this brother is not here
[laughter] this is you let's get the money sister
[clearing throat] he's already been returned maybe Hey okay mom truth or matha but he might not have a question we true or expect unexpected truth or dea truth or dea mom dea why people are running away truth eh ehe [clearing throat]
matha an
talk to kimaka ako ako
ah ah
push up three
push up three for k a normal thing
he might know today what to
do with a fist fist
no like this the
phone rang right there with a fist
that is like this with a fist
leave here we were dreaming of fire
being eaten
difficult things would you give him even money you
that is you really get a chance
[laughter]
do push up okay do push up
while ba someone got confused kaskia this
I love you
like ah like b someone got angry
[to hit go]
mat now right now he is the one who sees things are back to normal I do
n't know if you understand me
now he broke up with who his
father his children we told him call him tell him
I love you [laughter] he tells him
I love you while he is crying
[laughter] the
phone is crying [laughter]
mom let's aaha turn around let's do
your dea lord my god
bye baby
mom do deuki
push 3000
push
because I know 3,000 there you don't have
[laughter] it's gone it has
n't come back
that is
two
[laughter]
one more one more one more one more one more one more one
more
what was yours that was easy
come here come here like pushing him you twisted him
man I want to kill me
eh
what
m I wish I went to le
mom let's and he will get it let's give him a
challenge over there I am the one
asking questions I don't know at all you are dea you are
coming to me
paula
ahah
it's spinning again we're not what
we're going to do I don't know what
ahah there's
no you it doesn't mean it does
n't mean
there are people until they finish doing it guys why does
n't it want to that is
here I'm communicating with
my wife spiritually she wants me to go
all
you have to sell like this turn like this a thousand yes a thousand
zung a
thousand use force it spins a lot
[laughter] I ask us to
sit by giving each other space
[laughter]
he says
let's sit by giving each other space
you're holding don't
hold that down guys it's
not me sir
this
good
again like that
[laughter]
Truth de
tr
why truth and that one I
was dea you would dea
ask questions
ah yes I told you K I don't want him to get this
of mine I shouldn't be asked and K
ask this
if you don't have any questions m I'm coming here nagig
are you Straight
straight
guys.  Are you straight or not?  P
sexual.
What is that?
Pan section.
You know pansexual?
What is a pan section?
Google it.  Give us
straight answers.
No.  Actually I'm a supervisor.
What is it?
I'm killing a person who is
only in their head.
That identifies gender.
It identifies.
No.  it identifies
now you can't tell him
that's why I tell him look here is
sexual
what are you dating [laughter]
sexual who are you
let's look on your phone
saposexual means he only dates
intelligent people now that's gender no
you're confused what's up
no sir let's answer that is this are
you straight or gay the
answers are two
I'm not gay straight
okay the
answer here is who is
binary
non binary [laughter] because his question
I failed come here non binary
eh let's finish it leave guys I'm coming in at night it's already come they
said it's out that
p what is it what is it Google on the way
will explain to us in the car there's
no
and you're spinning it around it's spinning around
hard Eh let's
have a bottle it was
wait this here this here this here not here with
it [laughter]
here sir
go there it's you
look at me I'm coming look at who
there you saw you agreed I didn't ask [
laughter]
I mean there's
someone I don't give dea
[laughter]
bless you
wait sister Kajala where are you going they start
giving people answers
they've already closed there let's do it  let's leave they're closed so it's
impossible
I'm forgiven I'm
not impossible let's finish let's leave
[crying]
and we've done everything there when
it ends
still sh
even this one and sh still
this time
already still sh only who we'll catch
already has been asked
what
has been asked not asked yet you you you are
very busy
[laughter]
ask him then I'm not here you told him a thousand I tell you he
didn't tell me I mean
today he said here quickly
I just know [laughter] it's not smart
[clearing throat]
what do you regret about your current boyfriend
who I have right now
m how
many lovers does he have i.e.
out of your lovers you've had the one you're with main what do you
regret main character
main character
if you don't have
anything like that if you don't have main it's also
okay guys we said that he doesn't have
many lovers
no if he doesn't have anything he regrets yes ah there's nothing
to tell me
my current boyfriend
eh that is what you're saying
I just feel it's because he's known
m
yeah i don't like what he says here
not what he says to his partner kajala can I
tell you the truth i  I don't like that from the
bottom of my heart, I just seduced her for
seven years
and she is a good person,
so how long have you been in a relationship
now?
Five months, five if not six,
out of seven years of seducing her.
Why are you crying,
Mhi
Moshi? [laughter]
You know she's crying for him, she's crying for you,
man. [laughter]
Go and surround her right here so she doesn't hear what I'm
talking about. And until she surrounds
you, make sure
you've reached her. She's gone.
Oh, how are you, babe?
Or let him go around let him go around then ask a question
ti
shoni you were in your place
shoni it's me here already shoni come on
sir shoni
there he was
[laughter] trutike
truth
de
speak strongly
tell Paulo I hate you I hate you [
laughter]
I hate
ahahwi kumkumb [laughter]
I heard
you know melia mwenzio [laughter]
you paid
gently let's go this let's go
this sir no it's not a game
[laughter] he's
really crying
sh your mwenzio how he says he
loves you how could you say now
just now
I just gave him money I don't have money
[laughter] there
truth when he was going
around When I couldn't
tell him I would give him money I don't have
money you would do
anything you would take him off since
[laughter] I'm hurt
that is in my top four I took you out
ah sh he didn't want to be among the people to
be sacrificed [laughter] I
really got you stuck with the people to be sacrificed Have
you hurt your mwenzio?   I mean,
if I were to say that myself, I would
cry.
[music]
So guys, I built you here when I was
pregnant, we came with my mother but I
couldn't take pictures, I couldn't
enjoy it at first, I was very fast, so
on the boat itself I put on clothes
that weren't there,
I told her, mom, we have to go back to this
place, why did you say anything, am I
lying or are you not lying, sir, you
were pregnant, so I will show you there the
pictures I took of you when
I was pregnant.
So today I went back to Imagine with my child.
I can't wait for tomorrow when there will be boats and horses, we will
sail on that side. Today
he told us we are sleeping there,
we are asking if we will eat.
Let's go first and see
what's up, Alfu.
I want to see Rumkula Nyama but
there's a food that's passing by,
eh,
radi meat.
Okay, okay, we'll look at the top right away.
Then we'll tell you
okay. You'll also want to go and bring us up to the room and
visit again. It'll be fine. Thank you.
Thank you.
So I remember, guys, take the rooms on
this side. I've never slept here before.
Even I'm not used to it.
This is my third time coming here. I'm coming here for the
first time.
I don't want
this.
Hit him and kill him. He's helped me
a lot and I'm going on this trip. Don't turn off this.
Keep being a rich
aunt like that.  Okay
for the deposit.
Oh and also he bought her a gift of that kind of stuff
we went down with
because he dealt with Amara
Shesh his sister himself works he sees it
that is this my dress had a button
I asked the spirit to sew the button for me he sewed it I
left his needle in
Paula's jacket Paula is wearing a jacket he found
Sindan we want to prank Roy Sindan I stabbed
Paula like there here I
want me to go on a show
here I want me to go on a show
you are smart that is you are sitting there
drinking alcohol that is you are smart you are
not your word this here you have been brought in
Paula's jacket it stabbed Paula as she cries
No
eh what are you knocking on?
Ahah no, I mean I didn't do it on purpose, I
didn't leave it there on purpose.
Your Riano didn't have to take your gadget and
put it away.  This has put the partner out of his
misery.  Hey,
I'm sorry.  online that is he doesn't know that is me
ah
now you bro really what did
you leave there
why did you say you made a statement
ahah no that is I'm trying to record back
that if I left you can't
believe he
asked for his coat right now he's wearing it that's why he's
shocked that is he's sitting
down there the needle im so your friend
has a hole in your butt
that is a person who is a prostitute in the coat
where was the coat it was in the room
I don't know how I caught it I don't prick my friend if
you take him to the hospital how are you sitting I don't know how come come on come on come on
where
[laughter]
oh my god but I don't prick [crying] yes we
saw it we said come on let's prank you [
laughter]
alcohol has turned
bad [music
]
[music]
I told him that yesterday I didn't like
what
he told me he hates me I
really felt bad you know that's
why I woke up with it
or let's give him cornflakes
you want some cornflakes if he's going to
drink it with him he won't act like
that
[music]
Hello my people.
Our Arusha trip is still ongoing.
We were at the Grand Melia,
went to Ngorongoro, and then
went to Maryem.
What have we come to now?
The elephant.  The elephant.
So we will be here in Ngariso.  There are a
few activities we will do and
then we will continue.  We'll go to Moshi in the city,
do other things and all that.
But today we are in Ngarisel and right now
we are having a hearty breakfast.  Like
you see in the old sun like this.
Hmm.  What did God tell us
or what do you think?  Don't you know?
Oh
no,
no, why haven't they put pepper on them? They haven't put pepper on them.
So when
they call them,
what do we want? They need to call
100 to ask about social media.
What are they for?
over there
[music]
So guys, this is the boat that made us
come back again, I'm
scared
but I just want to take cute pictures.
Who is Amara's mother carrying?
Wait, whatever, calm down, calm down,
what about the lady, who do
you really want someone with experience?
He wants to sleep with you, you are
standing,
that's why it's a
joke,
oh my,
his sister would ride
this boat, I'll watch
you, you're pregnant with the express, I'm pregnant,
or do you think he started driving this boat
yesterday,
this one here is enjoying himself,
these days you don't let him go, or what, why
brother,
and why don't you let him go
these days, you just gave me an
order, I would go and leave everything at
once, oh just a
bug, you mention it, oh
let's just go,
peace, he'll watch, that is, while he's standing,
mom, or let's pass his sister, let's go back,
oh he
wants to stand and drive this, I'll let him drive,
drive, then
why are you bothering your parents today, he's pushing it, he'll push it, he ca
n't,
man,
now you've seen how you're being cut off, if it weren't for
dad, I wouldn't have come with
him because he says, since
you're leaving him to himself, leave me, he'll bother me,
go with him, I
can't enjoy myation, guys, I'm not going with
him, maybe it's just his birthday, I'll travel
with him, but after that, mom, you'll clean up
again, and the
answer is,
that's it, he's sitting quietly, yes.
[music]
[music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [music] [
music] [music] [music] yes
master
m
this is the master
okay
master yes oil
Okay.
other
[music]
[music] what
do you say?
I am sending it to Kajala Masanja.  Why are you all
giving us these things?   I mean, I
want you to give me
this as evidence of divorce tomorrow, when you're arguing with me, so that you don't have time.   Let
's read the schedule.
Our schedule at 3:00 is bush
breakfast.  We will have breakfast with the
animals.
Hmm.
Then at exactly 4:00 PM we will feed the animals on
the balcony.  Feeding on the balcony.
Then at 4:30 we have feeding at the bush.
We are going to feed the animals in the bush.  Then at
4 o'clock, this time at 4:30 o'clock, there is
Love with animals,
we have to dress
properly as if we were going to a
sports meeting.
Now I don't understand.
There will be love, behind the love
there will be animals playing.  So it's
like lunch or dinner, whatever,
but it will be like that.  And then at t:30
there will be a pool decoration with
animals.  In other words, your pool will be
decorated and decorated the way they
want to decorate it, based on who
you are.  And then there will be
animals.
Then there's host riding, we'll do it at
six.  There is bicycle riding.  The horse is
riding.  We will do this here anytime.
Gym and sauna.  K must do it early
before anything else.  Yes, I'm knocking on
the door, mind you, he hears me, even though I'm
so full, you
know, I have a fever, I don't have clothes for all these things,
I only have a horse's clothes, even the
swimming pool itself, the horse you have, we have a love
with animals.
Which one?
We said we had clothes worth I don't know
what.  Yes, we wear it here.  You have a
red dress you were carrying, I remember the document,
let's take this dress, I do
n't have shoes,
we will look for it, it's not an issue and you are still there,
it's a food allowance and what is this food allowance, you will be paid and I do
n't want to go on,
please give it to me,
what is this,
this is a paper
with a schedule, everyone must have it, I'm giving it to you
because I don't want you to lie to me tomorrow
and you don't tell me I didn't tell you because
on the phone you can say, look, this
is our time table for tomorrow, should I
read it for you or will you read it yourself
because there is a schedule that you are also on
your own.  [clearing throat]
I'm alone.
Who doesn't go to the gym here?
Like here, I can't do the gym.
You make me do the gym.  do you are a gym person
you how you
eh then gym I've been born who
m
known as a person of what
eh jim j
then
my parents who just called me jim it's
possible
[music]
[music] [music] [music] [music] [music
]
[music]
My name is
life wake up it won't let go I've had a big drink
do
but it only hurts on this side
okay
even though I wear glasses I forgot my glasses
the day I had them
but I don't think it's for glasses
because it has
pressure 121
it's okay
so is our oxygen level okay the
oxygen concentration level is is
okay pressure
but the the blood pressure is also okay
and The pass rate is relatively very
painful lab some of them want to
mix it with injection who liven
m
now maybe I'll ask will you prefer to
do it
now it's da gun
gunsaka
its maumiv is normal normal not
eh
others those who don't want to
hear it right
after injection somebody is sleepy
sorry
[music]
you're afraid
[laughter]
m I'm afraid of this one here I'm afraid of
this one it looks like they're not right
i.e. he can stab you  all anything
[music]
[music] Hold on, hold on
.  he's spitting at me, guys,
come on, come on a little bit, come on,
spit like spit,
come on
there [music]
hi guys, guys,
today is our last day, tomorrow
we have to go, I mean tomorrow night we're leaving, guys, guys,
I'm very sad, I'll catch up, I really enjoyed it.
This is our third hotel called A
Sopia.
We came here to feed the twigger and zebra.
So yeah, I'll catch up, guys.
We have to leave here at around 9 o'clock,
go to Moshi, see my little sister, and continue
with other things until it's time for the airport.
So yeah, bye.  by
[music]
So guys, it's time to go back home.
We really enjoyed Arusha and Moshi.
We had fun.
Amara has enjoyed disturbing us, although not too
much.  So I love my people of Arusha
very much.  See you next time.  What do you
have to say?
I'm
tired.   Are
you tired?
I miss my baby.
Hey guys, don't stop supporting us,
we love you so much.  Don't forget to
subscribe, like, comment and share.  Love
you.  See you guys in the next vlog.
Mahir